# Vu Huynh

Binh Thanh District ,Ho Chi Minh City



vu.huynhanh102@gmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/vu-huynh-2470232 in



https://windev.vercel.app



As a Front-end developer with 2+ years of experience in web development, adaptation, and maintenance. Currently seeking a position in web and application development with the opportunity to contribute, grow and expand current skill sets.

#### **Skills**

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

- Working knowledge in APIs, JavaScript, HTML, CSS,TypeScript, ReactJS, NextJS, NestJS, NodeJS, ExpressJS, Redux, Zustand, GraphQL TailwindCSS, Socket.IO, Firebase, Prisma Experienced with Git, GitHub. Gitlab,
- Postman, DBeaver, Docker SEM, SEO, Responsive web design

#### **SOFT SKILLS**

- English, Teamwork
- A fast learner, self-motivated, and hardworking individual
- Collaborative team player and self-starter
- Problem solver with the ability to analyze and prioritize difficult tasks

#### **Experience**

### Front-end Developer / MintIII (NFT Editor)

Front-end: Typescript, NextJS, Zustand, TailwindCSS, React Query, Mantine (Deploy on AWS) Back-end: Typescript, NestJS, RestAPI, MySQL, Swagger, AWS, Smart Contract (Deploy on AWS)

Deployment: <a href="https://mintiii-frontend-staging.vercel.app">https://mintiii-frontend-staging.vercel.app</a>

Team size: 10

**APRIL - JUNE 2023** 

#### Front/Back-End Developer / ChiChi Store (E-commerce website)

Front-end: Typescript, NextJS, Zustand, TailwindCSS (Deploy on vercel)

Back-end: Typescript, NestJS, Swagger API, RestAPI, MySQL (Deploy on render)

Deployment: <a href="https://chichi-store.vercel.app">https://chichi-store.vercel.app</a>

JANUARY - FEBRUARY 2023

#### Front/Back-End Developer / WSocial (Social network website)

Front-end: Typescript, NextJS, Redux, TailwindCSS (Deploy on vercel)

Back-end: NodeJS, ExpressJS, Typescript, Socket.IO, Prisma, GraphQL, MySQL (Deploy on render)

Deployment: <a href="https://wsocial.vercel.app">https://wsocial.vercel.app</a>

Github: https://github.com/windev1108/wsocial

**DECEMBER 2022 – FEBRUARY 2023** 

#### Front-end Developer / Personal Portfolio

Front-end: VueJS, Typescript, TailwindCSS (Deploy on vercel)

Deployment: <a href="https://windev.vercel.app">https://windev.vercel.app</a>

Github: <a href="https://github.com/windev1108/personal-portfolio">https://github.com/windev1108/personal-portfolio</a>

SEPTEMBER - OCTOBER 2022

## Front/Back-end Developer / Sport-yard (Soccer field booking website)

Front-end: **Typescript**, **NextJS**, **TailwindCSS**, **Redux** (Deploy on vercel) Back-end: **NodeJS**, **ExpressJS**, **Firebase**, **Socket.io** (Deploy on render)

Deployment: <a href="https://sport-yard.vercel.app">https://sport-yard.vercel.app</a>

Github: https://github.com/windev1108/sport-yard

**AUGUST - DECEMBER 2022** 

#### Front-end Developer / Diffcord (Realtime chat website)

Front-end: ReactJS, Javascript, Firebase, Redux, TailwindCSS, WebRTC(PeerJS) (Deploy on Firebase

hosting)

Deployment: https://diffcord.live

Github: https://github.com/windev1108/diffcord

**MAY 2022 - JUNE 2022** 

## Front-end Developer / WinFilm

Front-end: Javascript, React, TailwindCSS, Redux, Firebase, API 2embed movie (Deploy on Firebase

hosting)

Deployment : <a href="https://winphim-react.web.app">https://winphim-react.web.app</a>

Github: https://github.com/windev1108/winphim-react

JUNE – AUGUST 2021

#### **Education & Certification**

JANUARY- Present

# **Var-meta / Software Company**

Position: Software Engineer

AUGUST 2019 - DECEMBER 2022

# **Web Programming / FPT Polytechnic College**

Graduated in December 2022